(Sheldon:)Oh, glare.
(Penny:)But on the other hand...
(Penny:)...if things don't go well with Leonard,
I risk losing a really good friend.
I mean, he's not looking for a fling.
He's the kind that gets into a relationship
for, like you would say, light-years.
(Sheldon:)I would not say that.
No one would say that.
A light-year is a unit of distance, not time.
(Penny:)Thank you for the clarification.
(Sheldon:)Draft.
You see, people hear the word "year"
and they think duration.
Foot-pound has the same problem.
That's a unit of work, not of weight.
(Penny:)Right. Thanks.
- It's a common mistake.
- Not the first one I've made today.
(Sheldon:)Okay.
(Sheldon:)I think this will be my seat.
(Penny:)Do you have anything to say
that has anything to do...
(Penny:)...with, you know,
what I'm talking about?
(Sheldon:)Well, let's see.